A Register of the Records of the Russkaia sredniaia shkola (Paris, France)Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office file, 1920-1997 and undated. (Box 1)
  - Student records
    - Chertkova, Ekaterina (Folder 16: 11)
    - Chertkova, Elizaveta (Folder 16: 12)
    - Chertkova, Nataliia (Folder 16: 13)
    - Chikhanovich, Anna (Folder 16: 14)
    - Chimishkian, Virginia (Folder 16: 15)
    - Chirikova, Tat'iana (Folder 16: 16)
    - Chistochanov, Sergei (Folder 16: 17)
    - Chizinskii, Nikolai (Folder 16: 18)
    - Chizova, Irina (Folder 16: 19)
    - Chubar', Bianka (Folder 16: 20)
    - Dakhin, Nikolai (Folder 16: 21)
    - Damaskina, Tat'iana (Folder 16: 22)
    - Damershchikov, Mr. (Folder 16: 23)
    - Danilenko, Lidiia (Folder 16: 24)
    - Danilevich, Elena (Folder 16: 25)
    - Danil'chenko, Dimitrii (Folder 16: 26)
    - Danil'chenko, Petr (Folder 16: 27)
    - Dankevich-Kozub, Tamara (Folder 16: 28)
    - Danochkina, Aleksandra (Folder 16: 29)
    - Darekii, Sergei (Folder 16: 30)
    - Datsenko, Mikhail (Folder 16: 31)
    - Datsenko, Petr (Folder 16: 32)
    - Davydov, Anatolii (Folder 16: 33)
    - Davydov, Viktor (Folder 16: 34)
    - Davydova, Elena (Folder 16: 35)
    - Davydova, Liudmila (Folder 16: 36)
    - Debaibieux, Stefan (Folder 16: 37)
    - Dekhterev, Lionel (Folder 16: 38)
    - Delitsina, Tat'iana (Folder 16: 39)
    - Dembno-Chaikovskii, Mikhail (Folder 16: 40)
    - Dembo, Georgii (Folder 16: 41)
    - Demchenko, Ioann (Folder 16: 42)
    - Demchenko, Igor' (Folder 16: 43)
    - Demchinskii, Sviatoslav (Folder 16: 44)
    - Demidov, Georgii (Folder 16: 45)
    - Demiur, Aleksei (Folder 16: 46)
    - Demiur, Dimitrii (Folder 16: 47)
    - Denischuk, Nataliia (Folder 16: 48)
    - Denisov, Elizaveta (Folder 16: 49)
    - Denisov, Svetlana (Folder 16: 50)
    - Depre-Biksio, Mariia (Folder 16: 51)
    - Derevitskii, Nikolai (Folder 16: 52)
    - Deropinskii, Dimitrii (Folder 16: 53)
    - Derviz, Andrei (Folder 16: 54)
    - Derzhavich, Boris (Folder 16: 55)
    - Desh, Ol'ga (Folder 16: 56)
    - Diachkov-Tarasov, Evgenii (Folder 16: 57)
    - Diadik, Andrei (Folder 16: 58)
    - Diatlov, Aleksei (Folder 16: 59)
    - Dimitrieva, Ol'ga (Folder 16: 60)
    - Disterlo, Elena (Folder 16: 61)
    - Diumin, Dem'ian (Folder 16: 62)
    - Diumin, Nikolai (Folder 16: 63)
    - Diuperre, Kornelii (Folder 16: 64)
    - Diupon, Khristiana (Folder 16: 65)
    - Diushamen, Vladimir (Folder 16: 66)
    - Dmitrienko, Dimitrii (Folder 16: 67)
    - Dmitrieva, Tamara (Folder 16: 68)
    - Dobrovol'skaia, Evgeniia (Folder 16: 69)
    - Dobrynin, Georgii (Folder 16: 70)
    - Dobyzhinskii, Iolanta, and Valerian, and Veronika (Folder 16: 71)
    - Dodonov, Igor' (Folder 16: 72)
    - Dogel', Andrei (Folder 16: 73)
    - Dolgopolov, Aleksandr (Folder 16: 74)
    - Dolgopolov, Vadim (Folder 16: 75)
    - Dolgorukova, Nataliia (Folder 16: 76)
    - Dolinskaia, Tat'iana (Folder 16: 77)
    - Dolinskii, Igor' (Folder 16: 78)
    - Domanskii, Daniil (Folder 16: 79)
    - Dontsov, Ada, and Nikolai (Folder 16: 80)
    - Doriomedov, Iurii (Folder 16: 81)
    - Doroshenko, Pavel (Folder 16: 82)
    - Dorozhinskii, Vadim (Folder 16: 83)
    - Droen, Liudmila (Folder 16: 84)
    - Duban, Filip, and Irina (Folder 16: 85)
    - Dubentsev, Evgenii (Folder 16: 86)
    - Dubina, Elena (Folder 16: 87)
    - Dubrevskii, Vadim (Folder 16: 88)
    - Dubrovskii, Aleksei (Folder 16: 89)
    - Dudkovskii, Vitalii (Folder 16: 90)
    - Dunaeva, Tat'iana (Box-folder 17: 1)
    - Durasova, Antonina (Folder 17: 2)
    - Durova, Tat'iana (Folder 17: 3)
    - Dvorkin, Samuil (Folder 17: 4)
    - Dzhabagieva, Zara, and Zarema (Folder 17: 5)
    - Dzhavakhov, Iosif (Folder 17: 6)
    - Dimets, Dzhurdzhitsa (Folder 17: 7)
    - Diakova, Vera, and Zhakelin (Folder 17: 8)
    - Diakonova, Elizaveta, and Mariia (Folder 17: 9)
    - Edel'berg, Vladimir (Folder 17: 10)
    - Efdon, Mr. (Folder 17: 11)
    - Efimov, Georgii (Folder 17: 12)
    - Efremova, Nina (Folder 17: 13)
    - Egers, Nadezhda (Folder 17: 14)
    - Egorova, Zinaida (Folder 17: 15)
    - Ekk, Aleksander (Folder 17: 16)
    - Elachich, Mikhail, and Nataliia, and Nikolai (Folder 17: 17)
    - Eliseev, Nikita (Folder 17: 18)
    - Ellert, Nikolai (Folder 17: 19)
    - Elchaninov, Kirill, and Mariia (Folder 17: 20)
    - El'fimova, Irina (Folder 17: 21)
    - Emel'ianenko, Arkadii (Folder 17: 22)
    - Emel'ianov, Georgii (Folder 17: 23)
    - Emerik, Andrei (Folder 17: 24)
    - Enden, Marina, von (Folder 17: 25)
    - Engalychev, Mariia, and Nikolai, and Sofiia (Folder 17: 26)
    - En'ko-Danovskii, Nataliia, and Roman (Folder 17: 27)
    - Eremenko, Klavdiia (Folder 17: 28)
    - Ermakov, Mstislav (Folder 17: 29)
    - Ermakov, Petr (Folder 17: 30)
    - Ermoleev, Nikolai (Folder 17: 31)
    - Erokhin, Viacheslav (Folder 17: 32)
    - Ershov, Vladimir (Folder 17: 33)
    - Esman, Nikolai (Folder 17: 34)
    - Evdokimov, Mikhail (Folder 17: 35)
    - Evreinov, Aleksandr (Folder 17: 36)
    - Evseev, Anatolii (Folder 17: 37)
    - Evseevskii, Aleksei (Folder 17: 38)
    - Fabiano, Roberto (Folder 17: 39)
    - Fage, Tatiana (Folder 17: 40)
    - Falz-Fein, Aleksandr (Folder 17: 41)
    - Farkash, Irina, and Vladimir (Folder 17: 42)
    - Fedorenko, Vera (Folder 17: 43)
    - Fedorov, Mikhail (Folder 17: 44)
    - Fedorova, Liudmila, Nataliia (Folder 17: 45)
    - Fedorova, Nina (Folder 17: 46)
    - Fedos'ev, Aleksei, Liudmila (Folder 17: 47)
    - Fedotov, Dmitrii (Folder 17: 48)
    - Fedotov, Vladimir (Folder 17: 49)
    - Fedotova, Valentina (Folder 17: 50)
    - Feerchak, Boris (Folder 17: 51)
    - Fel'dan, Nataliia, and Nikolai (Folder 17: 52)
    - Ferlikovskaia, Irina, and Kseniia (Folder 17: 53)
    - Fetisova, Galina (Folder 17: 54)
    - Fialkovskii, Anna, and Boris, and Iurii, and Nataliia (Folder 17: 55)
    - Fidler, Iuliia, and Ol'ga, and Tatiana (Folder 17: 56)
    - Filippova, Anna (Folder 17: 57)
    - Filippova, Zoia (Folder 17: 58)
    - Filonov, Aleksandr, and Vladimir (Folder 17: 59)
    - Finkel'shtein, Irina, and Nina (Folder 17: 60)
    - Finkel'shtein, Lev (Folder 17: 61)
    - Fitiugov-Sheel', Oleg (Folder 17: 62)
    - Flamburari, Anatolii (Folder 17: 63)
    - Fleizer, Mikhail (Folder 17: 64)
    - Flerova, Viktoriia (Folder 17: 65)
    - Flige, Nikolai, and Vladimir (Folder 17: 66)
    - Fortunato, Mikhail, and Vladimir (Folder 17: 67)
    - Frakman, Georgii (Folder 17: 68)
    - Frederiks, Nikolai (Folder 17: 69)
    - Frid, Elena (Folder 17: 70)
    - Fride, Georgii (Folder 17: 71)
    - Fridlender, Sofiia (Folder 17: 72)
    - Frimerman, Iakov (Folder 17: 73)
    - Fruchedzhi, Dimitrii (Folder 17: 74)
    - Fuks, Gershon (Folder 17: 75)
    - Gabartina, Sara (Folder 17: 76)
    - Gabel', Aleksei (Folder 17: 77)
    - Gaburdin, Pierre (Folder 17: 78)
    - Gagarin, Grigorii (Folder 17: 79)
    - Gagen, Georgii (Folder 17: 80)
    - Gal'chinskii, Fedor (Folder 17: 81)
    - Galiaev, Oleg (Folder 17: 82)
    - Gall, Eduard (Folder 17: 83)
    - Galladzheva, Nina (Folder 17: 84)
    - Gallenshtein, Nataliia (Folder 17: 85)
    - Gamzikov, Mikhail (Folder 17: 86)
    - Gandurin, Elena, and Kira, and Nikolai (Folder 17: 87)
    - Ganson, Aleksei (Folder 17: 88)
    - Gaponov, Nataliia (Box-folder 18: 1)
    - Garder, Konstantin, von (Folder 18: 2)
    - Garich, Fedor (Folder 18: 3)
    - Garon, Ekaterina (Folder 18: 4)
    - Garting, Marina, and Nina (Folder 18: 5)
    - Gashinskii, Aristarkh (Folder 18: 6)
    - Gavrilenko, Georgii, Neonila (Folder 18: 7)
    - Gavrilov, Mikhail (Folder 18: 8)
    - Gazeev, Vladimir (Folder 18: 9)
    - Geisman, Pavel (Folder 18: 10)
    - Geitsig, Igor' (Folder 18: 11)
    - Gekimian, Konstantin (Folder 18: 12)
    - Gel'd, Pavel (Folder 18: 13)
    - Gemmerle, Ol'ga (Folder 18: 14)
    - Genichta, Nataliia (Folder 18: 15)
    - Genkel'-Berg, Sergei (Folder 18: 16)
    - Georgiev, Georgii, and Nadezhda (Folder 18: 17)
    - Georgits, Evgeniia (Folder 18: 18)
    - Georgiu, Nikolai (Folder 18: 19)
    - Gerbil'skii, Aleksei (Folder 18: 20)
    - Gering, Georgii (Folder 18: 21)
    - Geroeva, Nina (Folder 18: 22)
    - Gess, Alina (Folder 18: 23)
    - Gessel', Igor' (Folder 18: 24)
    - Gilami, Liudmila (Folder 18: 25)
    - Gil'bert, Nikolai (Folder 18: 26)
    - Ginsberg, Leona (Folder 18: 27)
    - Ginsburg, Elena, and Mariia-Elizaveta (Folder 18: 28)
    - Giul'azizova, Nataliia (Folder 18: 29)
    - Giul'msirian, Sergei (Folder 18: 30)
    - Giutine, Marina (Folder 18: 31)
    - Gladueva, Nataliia (Folder 18: 32)
    - Glavatskii, Fedor (Folder 18: 33)
    - Glebezdine, Vera (Folder 18: 34)
    - Glebov, Tatiana (Folder 18: 35)
    - Gleizer, Iulii (Folder 18: 36)
    - Glikman, Evgeniia, and Nina (Folder 18: 37)
    - Glikamanas, Abramos (Folder 18: 38)
    - Godko, Sergei (Folder 18: 39)
    - Godlevskaia, Anna, and Suzanne (Folder 18: 40)
    - Gofman, Anna, Nikolai (Folder 18: 41)
    - Gogine, Ol'ga (Folder 18: 42)
    - Goier, Ekaterina (Folder 18: 43)
    - Gokhbaum-Loginova, G. (Folder 18: 44)
    - Gol'dberg, Eduard (Folder 18: 45)
    - Gol'denberg, Georgii (Folder 18: 46)
    - Gol'dovskii, Boris (Folder 18: 47)
    - Golikova, Nataliia (Folder 18: 48)
    - Golitsyn, Boris, and Mariia (Folder 18: 49)
    - Golitsyna, Praskov'ia (Folder 18: 50)
    - Golitsynskaia, Anatolii, and Elena (Folder 18: 51)
    - Golovin, Antonina, and Vladimir (Folder 18: 52)
    - Golovina, Irina, and Sofiia (Folder 18: 53)
    - Golovko, Tat'iana (Folder 18: 54)
    - Golubkov, Kirill (Folder 18: 55)
    - Golubov, Aleksandr (Folder 18: 56)
    - Golubovskaia, Valentina (Folder 18: 57)
    - Goncharov, Mikhail (Folder 18: 58)
    - Goncharov, Nikita (Folder 18: 59)
    - Gonorskii, Andrei (Folder 18: 60)
    - Gontsov, Vadim (Folder 18: 61)
    - Gorbacheva, Elena (Folder 18: 62)
    - Gorbuntsov, Elena, and Vladimir (Folder 18: 63)
    - Gordeev, Vladimir (Folder 18: 64)
    - Gordon, Emanuil (Folder 18: 65)
    - Gorelov, Boris, and Nadezhda (Folder 18: 66)
    - Gorlenko, Evgeniia (Folder 18: 67)
    - Gorlin, Matfei (Folder 18: 68)
    - Gorodnichenko, Aleksandr (Folder 18: 69)
    - Gorovenko, Ol'ga (Folder 18: 70)
    - Gorushko, Evgeniia (Folder 18: 71)
    - Gossein, Ibraim (Folder 18: 72)
    - Gracheva, Tat'iana (Folder 18: 73)
    - Graf, Vladimir (Folder 18: 74)
    - Grammshchikova, Kira (Folder 18: 75)
    - Gredinov, Tovii (Folder 18: 76)
    - Gredinova, Tamara (Folder 18: 77)
    - Grekov, Daniil, and Ekaterina, and Mariia (Folder 18: 78)
    - Grekov, Lev, and Nikolai, and Ol'ga, and Vladimir (Folder 18: 79)
    - Greshnov, Georgii (Folder 18: 80)
    - Griel'skii, Marria, and Tamara (Folder 18: 81)
    - Grigorenko, Mikhail (Folder 18: 82)
    - Grigorenko, Ol'ga (Folder 18: 83)
    - Grigor'ev, Andrei, and Irina (Folder 18: 84)
    - Grigorova, Kseniia (Box-folder 19: 1)
    - Grineva, Irina (Folder 19: 2)
    - Grinshtein, Aron (Folder 19: 3)
    - Grintsovskaia, Cecile (Folder 19: 4)
    - Gritsiuk, Tamara (Folder 19: 5)
    - Gromov, Iurii (Folder 19: 6)
    - Gronskii, Nikolai, and Nina (Folder 19: 7)
    - Grzhebin, Andrei (Folder 19: 8)
    - Grzhebina, Elena (Folder 19: 9)
    - Guchkov, Mikhail (Folder 19: 10)
    - Gudin, Georgii (Folder 19: 11)
    - Gudkov, Igor' (Folder 19: 12)
    - Gudkov, Sergei (Folder 19: 13)
    - Gudkova, Mariia (Folder 19: 14)
    - Guel', Yvette (Folder 19: 15)
    - Guillier, Alain Jean-Claude (Folder 19: 16)
    - Guliaevskii, Aleksandr (Folder 19: 17)
    - Gulunova, Tat'iana (Folder 19: 18)
    - Gumsko, Nikolai (Folder 19: 19)
    - Gunkevich, Irina, and Nataliia (Folder 19: 20)
    - Gurevich, Evganiia (Folder 19: 21)
    - Gurevich, Irina (Folder 19: 22)
    - Gurgenbekov, Pavel (Folder 19: 23)
    - Gurskii, Iurii (Folder 19: 24)
    - Gurvich, Natal'ia (Folder 19: 25)
    - Gusakovskii, Nikolai (Folder 19: 26)
    - Gusarov, Abil'-Zirei (Folder 19: 27)
    - Guseva, Natal'ia (Folder 19: 28)
    - Gussakovskii, Iurii (Folder 19: 29)
    - Gutner, Aleksandr (Folder 19: 30)
    - Gvozdev, Nikolai (Folder 19: 31)
    - Iakhimovich, Nikolai (Folder 19: 32)
    - Iakhontov, Vasilii (Folder 19: 33)
    - Iakimova, Mariia (Folder 19: 34)
    - Iakovlev, Georgii (Folder 19: 35)
    - Iakovlev, Iurii (Folder 19: 36)
    - Iakovleva, Oksana (Folder 19: 37)
    - Iakovleva, Viktoriia (Folder 19: 38)
    - Iakubovskii, Petr (Folder 19: 39)
    - Ialyshev, Iurii (Folder 19: 40)
    - Ianaki, Larissa (Folder 19: 41)
    - Ianchevskaia, Mariia (Folder 19: 42)
    - Ianchevskii, Nikolai (Folder 19: 43)
    - Ianishevskaia, Irina (Folder 19: 44)
    - Iannovich, Mikhail (Folder 19: 45)
    - Iasinskii, Boris, and Tat'iana (Folder 19: 46)
    - Iatsenko, Nikolai (Folder 19: 47)
    - Iazykova, Ariadna, and Georgii, and Iziaslav (Folder 19: 48)
    - Ievleva, Marina (Folder 19: 49)
    - Ignat'ev, Dimitrii (Folder 19: 50)
    - Ignatov, Vladimir (Folder 19: 51)
    - Ikonnikov, Iaroslav, and Oleg (Folder 19: 52)
    - Ilichup, Alla (Folder 19: 53)
    - Il'ina, Elena (Folder 19: 54)
    - Il'ina, Irina (Folder 19: 55)
    - Il'ina, Lidiia (Folder 19: 56)
    - Il'inskaia, Irina, and Mariia (Folder 19: 57)
    - Il'iushkina, Lidiia, and Ol'ga (Folder 19: 58)
    - Illigevskii, Georgii (Folder 19: 59)
    - Ilovaiskii, Mark (Folder 19: 60)
    - Inver, Tat'iana (Folder 19: 61)
    - Ippolitov, Al'bert, and Siuzanna, and Zhannet (Folder 19: 62)
    - Isaev, Nikolai (Folder 19: 63)
    - Iudin-Bel'skii, Konstantin, and Veronika (Folder 19: 64)
    - Iunanov, Antonina, and Klavdiia, and Nadezhda, and Vladimir (Folder 19: 65)
    - Iungmeister, Nikolai (Folder 19: 66)
    - Iur, Viktoriia (Folder 19: 67)
    - Iureneva (Bliznuik), Nataliia (Folder 19: 68)
    - Iur'ev, Vsevolod (Folder 19: 69)
    - Iurevich, Aleksandr, and Aleksei, and Igor' (Folder 19: 70)
    - Iurgens, Nataliia (Folder 19: 71)
    - Iurkovskaia, Kseniia (Folder 19: 72)
    - Iushkevich, Inassa (Folder 19: 73)
    - Iustis, James (Folder 19: 74)
    - Ivakno, Aleksandra, and Mariia, and Petr (Folder 19: 75)
    - Ivanov, Grigorii, and Iuiliia, and Nina, and Vadim, and Vladimir (Folder 19: 76)
    - Ivanov, Pavel, and Petr (Folder 19: 77)
    - Ivanov, Sergei (Folder 19: 78)
    - Ivanova, Anna-Iuliia (Folder 19: 79)
    - Ivanova, Ekaterina (Folder 19: 80)
    - Ivanova, Nataliia (Folder 19: 81)
    - Ivanova, Raissa (Folder 19: 82)
    - Ivanovskaia, Kirilla (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - Ivashkevich, Ekaterina (Folder 20: 2)
    - Ivchenko, Oleg (Folder 20: 3)
    - Ivinskii, Oleg (Folder 20: 4)
    - Ivkov, Georgii (Folder 20: 5)
    - Ivnitskii, Sergei (Folder 20: 6)
    - Izmailovich, Valentina (Folder 20: 7)
    - Kachanov, Nikolai (Folder 20: 8)
    - Kachkacheva, Magdalina, and Tamara (Folder 20: 9)
    - Kagan, Felitsiia (Folder 20: 10)
    - Kalantariants, Aida (Folder 20: 11)
    - Kalantarov, Edik (Folder 20: 12)
    - Kalashnikov, Evgenii (Folder 20: 13)
    - Kalenichenko, Pavel (Folder 20: 14)
    - Kalganova, Tat'iana (Folder 20: 15)
    - Kaliagin, Iurii (Folder 20: 16)
    - Kalif, Mikhail (Folder 20: 17)
    - Kaligas, Irina (Folder 20: 18)
    - Kalinin, Kirill (Folder 20: 19)
    - Kalinskii, Georgii (Folder 20: 20)
    - Kaliuzhnyi, Aleksandr, and Aleksei (Folder 20: 21)
    - Kalmykov, Iurii, Nataliia (Folder 20: 22)
    - Kalmykova, Nina (Folder 20: 23)
    - Kal'nitskaia, Mariia (Folder 20: 24)
    - Kaminskaia, Irina, Nataliia, Tat'iana (Folder 20: 25)
    - Kaminskii, Petr (Folder 20: 26)
    - Kamkina, Tat'iana (Folder 20: 27)
    - Kamp, Andrei, and Elena (Folder 20: 28)
    - Kamsik, Mikhail (Folder 20: 29)
    - Kanaki, Tat'iana (Folder 20: 30)
    - Kandaurov, V. (Folder 20: 31)
    - Kantorovich, Samuil (Folder 20: 32)
    - Kan-Kagan, Maks (Folder 20: 33)
    - Kapari, Vladimir (Folder 20: 34)
    - Kapitovich, Irina (Folder 20: 35)
    - Kapnist, Emiliia, and Pavel (Folder 20: 36)
    - Karamyshev, Aleksandr (Folder 20: 37)
    - Karandakova, Tat'iana (Folder 20: 38)
    - Karaulova, Nataliia (Folder 20: 39)
    - Karbasnikov, Igor', and Nikolai (Folder 20: 40)
    - Karlinskii, Nataliia, and Varvara, and Vasilii (Folder 20: 41)
    - Karpenko, Anton (Folder 20: 42)
    - Karpenko, Dimitrii (Folder 20: 43)
    - Karpikhina, Svetlana (Folder 20: 44)
    - Karpinioti, Mariia (Folder 20: 45)
    - Karpov, Lidiia, and Sergei (Folder 20: 46)
    - Karpovich, Arsenii (Folder 20: 47)
    - Kashkin, Sergei, Vera (Folder 20: 48)
    - Kashnitskii, Aleksei (Folder 20: 49)
    - Kashtalinskii, Igor' (Folder 20: 50)
    - Kasperov, Nikolai (Folder 20: 51)
    - Kasso, Konrad (Folder 20: 52)
    - Katseblina, Tat'iana (Folder 20: 53)
    - Katnar, Boris (Folder 20: 54)
    - Katyk, Elena, and Il'ia (Folder 20: 55)
    - Kavos, Stefan (Folder 20: 56)
    - Kavun, Konstantin (Folder 20: 57)
    - Kazaderok, Evgeniia, Maksim (Folder 20: 58)
    - Kazakevich, Aleksandr (Folder 20: 59)
    - Kazanokova, Kukusia (Folder 20: 60)
    - Kazanova, Irina (Folder 20: 61)
    - Kedrova, Irina (Folder 20: 62)
    - Kefeli, Iusuf (Folder 20: 63)
    - Keller, Boris (Folder 20: 64)
    - Kenig, Erna (Folder 20: 65)
    - Keppen, Georgii, and Mikhail (Folder 20: 66)
    - Kerner, Georgii, and Vera (Folder 20: 67)
    - Kernozhitskii, Dimitrii (Folder 20: 68)
    - Kesarev, Valentin (Folder 20: 69)
    - Kessel'man, Oleg (Folder 20: 70)
    - Kessler, Nina (Folder 20: 71)
    - Kgaevskii, Oleg (Folder 20: 72)
    - Khachaturiants, Viktoriia (Folder 20: 73)
    - Khakhutova, Anna (Folder 20: 74)
    - Khaleeva, Lidiia (Folder 20: 75)
    - Khaliutina, Anna (Folder 20: 76)
    - Kharbiuzov, Georgii (Folder 20: 77)
    - Khardinskaia, Evgeniia (Folder 20: 78)
    - Kharin, Igor' (Folder 20: 79)
    - Kharitonova, Irina (Folder 20: 80)
    - Kharitonovskii, Nikolai (Folder 20: 81)
    - Kharlamov, Vsevolod (Folder 20: 82)
    - Kharlamova, Evgeniia (Folder 20: 83)
    - Kharmanskaia, Nadezhda (Folder 20: 84)
    - Khazin, Aleksandr, and Elena (Box-folder 21: 1)
    - Khazov, Aleksandr (Folder 21: 2)
    - Khenkin, Kirill (Folder 21: 3)
    - Khinkis, Evgeniia (Folder 21: 4)
    - Khioni, Iurii (Folder 21: 5)
    - Khitrovo, Sergei (Folder 21: 6)
    - Khlebnikova, Liudmila (Folder 21: 7)
    - Khmarin, Mariia, and Nikolai (Folder 21: 8)
    - Khodalitskii, Vladimir (Folder 21: 9)
    - Khodzhash, Aleksandr (Folder 21: 10)
    - Kholutova, Evgeniia (Folder 21: 11)
    - Khopelidze, Lidiia (Folder 21: 12)
    - Khorkevich, Galina (Folder 21: 13)
    - Khoroshun, Konstantin (Folder 21: 14)
    - Khoshabaeva, Elizaveta (Folder 21: 15)
    - Khrentovich-Buteneva, Ekaterina (Folder 21: 16)
    - Khreshtitskii, Aleksandr (Folder 21: 17)
    - Khristoforova, Anna (Folder 21: 18)
    - Khrizman, Isaak (Folder 21: 19)
    - Khuk, Mikhail, von (Folder 21: 20)
    - Khvalynskii, Klavdii, and Nikolai (Folder 21: 21)
    - Khvostova, Nataliia (Folder 21: 22)
    - Kianskii, Ivan (Folder 21: 23)
    - Kikin, Nikolai (Folder 21: 24)
    - Kirkwood, Viktor (Folder 21: 25)
    - Kirsanov, Anatolii (Folder 21: 26)
    - Kir'ianenko, Aleksei (Folder 21: 27)
    - Kiselev, Nataliia, Sergei (Folder 21: 28)
    - Kiseleva-Mironova, Ariadna (Folder 21: 29)
    - Kiselevskaia, Tat'iana (Folder 21: 30)
    - Kislyi, Maksim (Folder 21: 31)
    - Klafton, Gertrude (Folder 21: 32)
    - Klemm, Kirill, von (Folder 21: 33)
    - Klimakov, Konstantin (Folder 21: 34)
    - Klimantovich, Oleg (Folder 21: 35)
    - Klimchuk, Galina (Folder 21: 36)
    - Klimenko, Georgii (Folder 21: 37)
    - Klimov, Igor' (Folder 21: 38)
    - Klippel', Nina (Folder 21: 39)
    - Klineva, Nataliia (Folder 21: 40)
    - Klobukov, Andrei (Folder 21: 41)
    - Kobako, Nikolai (Folder 21: 42)
    - Kobieva, Nataliia (Folder 21: 43)
    - Kochan, Viktor (Folder 21: 44)
    - Kochetkova, Svetlana (Folder 21: 45)
    - Kofod, Oleg, and Irina (Folder 21: 46)
    - Koin-Karanvan, Aleksandr (Folder 21: 47)
    - Kokhamovskii, Khristian (Folder 21: 48)
    - Kokhno, Aleksandr (Folder 21: 49)
    - Kolchak, Aleksandr (Folder 21: 50)
    - Kolesnikov, Anatolii (Folder 21: 51)
    - Kolesnikov, Oleg (Folder 21: 52)
    - Kolesnikova, Dariia (Folder 21: 53)
    - Kolesnikova, Irina (Folder 21: 54)
    - Kolozev, Nikolai (Folder 21: 55)
    - Kobtsev, Igor' (Folder 21: 56)
    - Kolbasin, Mikhail (Folder 21: 57)
    - Kolif, Mikhail (Folder 21: 58)
    - Kolodkin, Evgenii, and Gennadii (Folder 21: 59)
    - Koloskova, Valentina (Folder 21: 60)
    - Kolovrat, Ol'ga (Folder 21: 61)
    - Kolpakova, Tat'iana (Folder 21: 62)
    - Kolzakova, Nataliia (Folder 21: 63)
    - Komarov, Georgii (Folder 21: 64)
    - Komarov, Sergei (Folder 21: 65)
    - Komerovskii, Iurii, and Sergei (Folder 21: 66)
    - Kondzerovskii, Kirill (Folder 21: 67)
    - Koniius, Boris (Folder 21: 68)
    - Koniius, Marianna (Folder 21: 69)
    - Kon'kov, Mikhail (Folder 21: 70)
    - Kononenko, Serafim, and Taisiia (Folder 21: 71)
    - Konorezov, Boris (Folder 21: 72)
    - Konoval'chenko, Elizaveta (Folder 21: 73)
    - Konovalov, Georgii (Folder 21: 74)
    - Konovalov, Ivan (Folder 21: 75)
    - Konovalova, Ekaterina (Folder 21: 76)
    - Konovitsin, Sergei (Folder 21: 77)
    - Konstantinov, Georgii, and Pavel (Folder 21: 78)
    - Konstantinova, Alla, and Ekaterina (Folder 21: 79)
    - Kopre, Iuliia (Folder 21: 80)
    - Korechnikov, Dimitrii (Folder 21: 81)
    - Korenev, Sergei (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - Koretskii, N. (Folder 22: 2)
    - Korfiatis, Antonii (Folder 22: 3)
    - Korganov, Grant (Folder 22: 4)
    - Korinev, Georgii (Folder 22: 5)
    - Korneichuk, Igor' (Folder 22: 6)
    - Kormenko, Elena (Folder 22: 7)
    - Kornilov, Dimitrii, and Kira, and Sergei (Folder 22: 8)
    - Korolev, Ekaterina (Folder 22: 9)
    - Korol'kov, Mikhail (Folder 22: 10)
    - Korostovets, Ivan (Folder 22: 11)
    - Korotkova, Aleksandra (Folder 22: 12)
    - Korvin-Krukovskii, Mikhail (Folder 22: 13)
    - Kosenko, Andrei (Folder 22: 14)
    - Korshlakova, Galina (Folder 22: 15)
    - Kosiuk, Irina (Folder 22: 16)
    - Kosmidi, Aleksandr (Folder 22: 17)
    - Kosminskii, Aleksei (Folder 22: 18)
    - Kostandi, Tat'iana (Folder 22: 19)
    - Kostenko, Igor' (Folder 22: 20)
    - Kostevich, Mikhail (Folder 22: 21)
    - Kostritskii, Leonid (Folder 22: 22)
    - Kostromin, Konstantin, and Ol'ga, and Pavel (Folder 22: 23)
    - Kosyi, Gi (Folder 22: 24)
    - Kotliar, Elizaveta (Folder 22: 25)
    - Kotliarov, Konstantin, and Nikolai (Folder 22: 26)
    - Kotoman, Nina (Folder 22: 27)
    - Kotomkina, Irina (Folder 22: 28)
    - Kotsarenko, Vladimir (Folder 22: 29)
    - Kotyrlo, Viktor (Folder 22: 30)
    - Kovalev, Stefan (Folder 22: 31)
    - Kovalevskaia, Marina (Folder 22: 32)
    - Kovalevskii, Evgraf (Folder 22: 33)
    - Koval'skii, Vladimir (Folder 22: 34)
    - Kozachevskii, Oleg (Folder 22: 35)
    - Kozakevich, Andrei (Folder 22: 36)
    - Kozakevich, Mikhail (Folder 22: 37)
    - Kozinets, Oleg, and Rostislav (Folder 22: 38)
    - Kozitskii, Inna, and Ivan (Folder 22: 39)
    - Kozlovskii, Georgii, and Igor', and Ol'ga, and Tat'iana, and Vera (Folder 22: 40)
    - Kozyrchuk, Mikhail (Folder 22: 41)
    - Kramarevskii, Vladimir (Folder 22: 42)
    - Kramarinskaia, Larissa (Folder 22: 43)
    - Krapotkina, Elena (Folder 22: 44)
    - Krasavina, Georgii, and Nina (Folder 22: 45)
    - Krasel'chik, Mikhail (Folder 22: 46)
    - Krasovskii, Aleksandr, and Georgii (Folder 22: 47)
    - Kravchenko, Nataliia (Folder 22: 48)
    - Kremenetskii, Vladimir (Folder 22: 49)
    - Krigshtein, Elena (Folder 22: 50)
    - Krinitskii, Sergei (Folder 22: 51)
    - Krinskaia, Irina (Folder 22: 52)
    - Krishevskii, Iurii (Folder 22: 53)
    - Kristi, Grigorii (Folder 22: 54)
    - Kriukov, Sergei (Folder 22: 55)
    - Krivoshein, Georgii (Folder 22: 56)
    - Krivoshein, Kirill (Folder 22: 57)
    - Krivuts, Irina (Folder 22: 58)
    - Krolevetskii, Vasilii (Folder 22: 59)
    - Kronskii, Evgenii (Folder 22: 60)